President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Website of the Office of the President, 2013 May 2 - 2017 July 17; 16; 83 Captures
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 May 2
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 May 8
    This item had no crawl rules.
    The CDX index for this capture did not contain crawl information.
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 May 8
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 June 5
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 June 5
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 July 1
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 September 11
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 September 11
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 October 1
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 January 1
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 January 1
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 February 5
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 February 5
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 March 26
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 March 26
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 July 9
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 July 9
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 July 16
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 July 16
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 September 17
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 September 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 October 22
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2014 October 22
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 7
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 7
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 14
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 14
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 28
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 January 28
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 4
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 February 4
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 29
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 April 29
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 6
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 6
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 13
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 13
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 27
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 May 27
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 3
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 3
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 10
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 June 10
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 July 17
    crawl: 165088
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2015-07-22T22:02:18Z
    end_date: 2015-07-22T21:28:19Z
    elapsed_ms: 448383534
    Crawl Types
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    pdfs_only: False
    test: False
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 432000
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 518483
    novel_count: 22064
    duplicate_count: 310947
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 185472
    downloaded_count: 333011
    download_failures: 280
    warc_revisit_count: 310940
    warc_url_count: 332912
    total_data_in_kbs: 92321075
    duplicate_bytes: 89386949991
    warc_compressed_bytes: 975896456
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.74
    kb_rate: 205.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 July 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 September 17
    crawl: 173356
    start_date: 2015-09-17T16:57:20Z
    original_start_date: 2015-09-17T16:57:20Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-09-23T01:24:03Z
    end_date: 2015-09-23T00:16:53Z
    elapsed_ms: 458363239
    discovered_count: 367719
    novel_count: 26001
    duplicate_count: 206766
    queued_count: 134952
    downloaded_count: 232767
    download_failures: 237
    warc_revisit_count: 206761
    warc_url_count: 232678
    total_data_in_kbs: 101606587
    duplicate_bytes: 94029637527
    warc_compressed_bytes: 157865634
    doc_rate: 0.51
    kb_rate: 221.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 September 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 17
    crawl: 179047
    start_date: 2015-10-17T16:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2015-10-17T16:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-10-22T19:45:11Z
    end_date: 2015-10-22T19:02:36Z
    elapsed_ms: 439557452
    discovered_count: 390211
    novel_count: 36614
    duplicate_count: 202550
    queued_count: 151047
    downloaded_count: 239164
    download_failures: 276
    warc_revisit_count: 202548
    warc_url_count: 239075
    total_data_in_kbs: 61075441
    duplicate_bytes: 53769145120
    warc_compressed_bytes: 6127282356
    doc_rate: 0.54
    kb_rate: 138.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 October 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 November 17
    crawl: 183657
    start_date: 2015-11-17T17:41:09Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-17T17:41:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-03T05:50:07Z
    end_date: 2015-11-30T19:18:26Z
    elapsed_ms: 432098049
    discovered_count: 415196
    novel_count: 17867
    duplicate_count: 229881
    queued_count: 167448
    downloaded_count: 247748
    download_failures: 242
    warc_revisit_count: 229876
    warc_url_count: 247648
    total_data_in_kbs: 61913750
    duplicate_bytes: 62091532709
    warc_compressed_bytes: 256259119
    doc_rate: 0.57
    kb_rate: 143.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2015 November 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 January 17
    crawl: 191947
    start_date: 2016-01-17T16:55:00Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-17T16:55:00Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-22T17:27:17Z
    end_date: 2016-01-22T16:56:58Z
    elapsed_ms: 432114027
    discovered_count: 573952
    novel_count: 20681
    duplicate_count: 273347
    queued_count: 279924
    downloaded_count: 294028
    download_failures: 181
    warc_revisit_count: 273342
    warc_url_count: 293928
    total_data_in_kbs: 63947333
    duplicate_bytes: 64312716410
    warc_compressed_bytes: 176478309
    doc_rate: 0.68
    kb_rate: 147.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 January 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 February 17
    crawl: 196723
    Crawl Rules
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ualbanysports.com (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for library.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for asrc.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for atmos.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for bioinformatics.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cela.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for choose.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cs.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for csda.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for imls.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cwig.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for events.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for hr.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for ibl.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for illiad.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for liblogs.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for libguides.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for scholarsarchive.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for listserv.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for m.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for omega.math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for mumford.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for nyjm.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for pdp.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for resnet.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cyberphysics.rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rna.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for slsc.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uaems.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uapps.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for wiki.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    start_date: 2016-02-17T16:57:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-17T16:57:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-23T04:10:10Z
    end_date: 2016-02-22T23:20:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 454987781
    discovered_count: 7638127
    novel_count: 795824
    duplicate_count: 806868
    queued_count: 6035435
    downloaded_count: 1602692
    download_failures: 248
    warc_revisit_count: 806856
    warc_url_count: 1602561
    total_data_in_kbs: 226292461
    duplicate_bytes: 193554304269
    warc_compressed_bytes: 633147239
    doc_rate: 3.52
    kb_rate: 497.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 February 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 6
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 18
    crawl: 201840
    start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-22T18:02:10Z
    end_date: 2016-03-22T16:56:57Z
    elapsed_ms: 432107388
    discovered_count: 639552
    novel_count: 138564
    duplicate_count: 332568
    queued_count: 168420
    downloaded_count: 471132
    download_failures: 1411433
    warc_revisit_count: 332563
    warc_url_count: 471037
    total_data_in_kbs: 116820623
    duplicate_bytes: 113225737713
    warc_compressed_bytes: 765920585
    doc_rate: 1.09
    kb_rate: 270.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 March 18
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 April 17
    crawl: 207692
    start_date: 2016-04-17T16:55:13Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-17T16:55:13Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-22T22:29:09Z
    end_date: 2016-04-22T18:00:08Z
    elapsed_ms: 435852385
    discovered_count: 7165982
    novel_count: 582992
    duplicate_count: 879835
    queued_count: 5703155
    downloaded_count: 1462827
    download_failures: 284
    warc_revisit_count: 879824
    warc_url_count: 1462700
    total_data_in_kbs: 227675763
    duplicate_bytes: 214936501775
    warc_compressed_bytes: 813502772
    doc_rate: 3.36
    kb_rate: 522.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 April 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 May 17
    crawl: 212937
    start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-24T10:38:52Z
    end_date: 2016-05-22T22:20:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 451503421
    discovered_count: 8685839
    novel_count: 568136
    duplicate_count: 1043240
    queued_count: 7074463
    downloaded_count: 1611376
    download_failures: 229
    warc_revisit_count: 1043205
    warc_url_count: 1611247
    total_data_in_kbs: 246906729
    duplicate_bytes: 230750229955
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2352496320
    doc_rate: 3.57
    kb_rate: 546.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 May 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 June 17
    crawl: 220038
    start_date: 2016-06-17T16:55:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-17T16:55:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-23T01:46:32Z
    end_date: 2016-06-22T19:28:00Z
    elapsed_ms: 441165235
    discovered_count: 8887536
    novel_count: 557229
    duplicate_count: 1067492
    queued_count: 7262815
    downloaded_count: 1624721
    download_failures: 247
    warc_revisit_count: 1067450
    warc_url_count: 1624592
    total_data_in_kbs: 251943396
    duplicate_bytes: 239433481575
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1787914405
    doc_rate: 3.68
    kb_rate: 571.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 June 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 July 17
    crawl: 225859
    start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-07-22T22:52:35Z
    end_date: 2016-07-22T17:55:28Z
    elapsed_ms: 435383503
    discovered_count: 6792375
    novel_count: 212820
    duplicate_count: 1098346
    queued_count: 5481209
    downloaded_count: 1311166
    download_failures: 256
    warc_revisit_count: 1098317
    warc_url_count: 1311042
    total_data_in_kbs: 212249210
    duplicate_bytes: 207609316437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 675349961
    doc_rate: 3.01
    kb_rate: 487.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 July 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
    crawl: 231044
    Block host dev.library.albany.edu
    start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-23T01:20:50Z
    end_date: 2016-08-22T23:33:45Z
    elapsed_ms: 455703830
    discovered_count: 1189467
    novel_count: 184079
    duplicate_count: 736427
    queued_count: 268961
    downloaded_count: 920506
    download_failures: 267
    warc_revisit_count: 736404
    warc_url_count: 920384
    total_data_in_kbs: 202254345
    duplicate_bytes: 198029314926
    warc_compressed_bytes: 397770039
    doc_rate: 2.02
    kb_rate: 443.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 August 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 October 17
    crawl: 243096
    start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-22T20:32:46Z
    end_date: 2016-10-22T17:07:30Z
    elapsed_ms: 432270469
    discovered_count: 1819420
    novel_count: 557303
    duplicate_count: 900445
    queued_count: 361672
    downloaded_count: 1457748
    download_failures: 296
    warc_revisit_count: 900407
    warc_url_count: 1457649
    total_data_in_kbs: 215568357
    duplicate_bytes: 201221539907
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1485925187
    doc_rate: 3.37
    kb_rate: 498.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 October 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 November 17
    crawl: 249672
    start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-22T23:26:30Z
    end_date: 2016-11-22T18:15:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 436686458
    discovered_count: 6455397
    novel_count: 904107
    duplicate_count: 647491
    queued_count: 4903799
    downloaded_count: 1551598
    download_failures: 287
    warc_revisit_count: 647445
    warc_url_count: 1551482
    total_data_in_kbs: 234676600
    duplicate_bytes: 166348006398
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22645478722
    doc_rate: 3.55
    kb_rate: 537.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 November 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 December 17
    crawl: 255339
    start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-22T23:02:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-22T17:39:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 434651176
    discovered_count: 5605147
    novel_count: 672626
    duplicate_count: 721586
    queued_count: 4210935
    downloaded_count: 1394212
    warc_revisit_count: 721559
    warc_url_count: 1394095
    total_data_in_kbs: 173161585
    duplicate_bytes: 152072050167
    warc_compressed_bytes: 4226018506
    doc_rate: 3.21
    kb_rate: 398.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2016 December 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
    crawl: 261028
    start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-23T00:48:05Z
    end_date: 2017-01-22T19:31:33Z
    elapsed_ms: 440845477
    discovered_count: 6856243
    novel_count: 810250
    duplicate_count: 844972
    queued_count: 5201021
    downloaded_count: 1655222
    download_failures: 351
    warc_revisit_count: 844920
    warc_url_count: 1655090
    total_data_in_kbs: 260833049
    duplicate_bytes: 210669517964
    warc_compressed_bytes: 15598206209
    doc_rate: 3.75
    kb_rate: 591.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 January 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 February 17
    crawl: 267806
    start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-22T23:52:19Z
    end_date: 2017-02-22T17:57:15Z
    elapsed_ms: 435595208
    discovered_count: 6181071
    novel_count: 757736
    duplicate_count: 820126
    queued_count: 4603209
    downloaded_count: 1577862
    download_failures: 339
    warc_revisit_count: 820090
    warc_url_count: 1577729
    total_data_in_kbs: 257873727
    duplicate_bytes: 232995142726
    warc_compressed_bytes: 5661819855
    doc_rate: 3.62
    kb_rate: 592.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 February 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
    crawl: 273971
    start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T22:25:00Z
    end_date: 2017-03-22T18:08:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 436406787
    discovered_count: 7409222
    novel_count: 690900
    duplicate_count: 1257496
    queued_count: 5460826
    downloaded_count: 1948396
    download_failures: 359
    warc_revisit_count: 1257455
    warc_url_count: 1948270
    total_data_in_kbs: 266864045
    duplicate_bytes: 245675593330
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1581675727
    doc_rate: 4.46
    kb_rate: 611.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 March 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
    crawl: 301465
    Host Rule Type C CONTAINS meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search? (last updated 2017-05-11)
    start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-23T00:29:43Z
    end_date: 2017-05-22T21:46:25Z
    elapsed_ms: 449440076
    discovered_count: 2923335
    novel_count: 388249
    duplicate_count: 1238165
    queued_count: 1296921
    downloaded_count: 1626414
    download_failures: 336
    warc_revisit_count: 1238113
    warc_url_count: 1626286
    total_data_in_kbs: 265327774
    duplicate_bytes: 251274786133
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3306915146
    kb_rate: 590.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 May 17
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 July 17
    crawl: 315280
    Applied scope rule: BLOCK_HOST for host dev.library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-08-09, last updated 2016-08-09)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host pbs.twimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host abs.twimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.youtube.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host s.pinimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host mobile.twitter.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host twitter.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host plus.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host yt3.ggpht.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host r19---sn-n4v7kn7e.googlevideo.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host es.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.pt (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host kr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.se (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host sk.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host dk.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ar.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fi.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host chrome.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host gaming.youtube.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cl.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host it.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)